[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This luxury U.S. car make was founded in 1902 from what had remained from the Henry Ford Company, and in 1909 it was bought by General Motors.", "correct_answer": "Cadillac", "incorrect_answers": ["Hummer", "Ford", "Chevrolet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sun contains about what percentage of the entire solar systems mass?", "correct_answer": "98%", "incorrect_answers": ["28%", "78%", "58%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award winning actress stars as Kelly Frears in the movie Cast Away?", "correct_answer": "Helen Hunt", "incorrect_answers": ["Meryl Streep", "Susan Sarandon", "Daryl Hannah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a level 4 (Transport Layer) network protocol?", "correct_answer": "RIP", "incorrect_answers": ["TCP", "UDP", "SPX"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Memento, Teddys phone number 555-0134 is identical to the number of which character from the movie Fight Club?", "correct_answer": "Marla Singer", "incorrect_answers": ["The Narrator", "Robert Bob Paulson", "Tyler Durden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is the average mudpuppy?", "correct_answer": "13-16 inches", "incorrect_answers": ["1 1/2 -3 inches", "5-7 inches", "12 inches"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What company introduced its popular entertainment system in 1985?", "correct_answer": "Nintendo", "incorrect_answers": ["Magnavox", "Sega", "Atari"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Owens Valley, the arid ranching valley of the Owens River, stretches for approximately 75 miles (120 km) on the territory of which US state?", "correct_answer": "California", "incorrect_answers": ["Arkansas", "Alabama", "Arizona"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these are not a function of a zebras stripes?", "correct_answer": "A warning sign to other zebras", "incorrect_answers": ["Identification within the herd", "Heat dissipation", "Confusion of predators"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does BTDT mean in instant messaging language?", "correct_answer": "been there, done that", "incorrect_answers": ["but I thought you didnt tell", "boy thats dirty talk", "better than doing time"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Corinth Canal separates this Greek peninsula from the mainland of Greece.", "correct_answer": "Peloponnese", "incorrect_answers": ["Halkidiki", "Mani", "Elounda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many people are overweight around the world?", "correct_answer": "More than 1 billion", "incorrect_answers": ["More than 3 million", "More than 1 million", "More than 5 million"]}]